Oh God said to Abraham,
Kill me a son
Abe says, "Man, you must be
puttin' me on"
God say, No. Abe say, What?
God say, You can do
what you want Abe, but
The next time you see me comin
you better run
Well Abe says, Where do you
want this killin done?
God says, Out on Highway 61
Well Georgia Sam
he had a bloody nose
Welfare Department they
wouldnt give him no clothes
He asked poor Howard
where can I go
Howard said theres only
one place I know
Sam said tell me quick man
I got to run
Ol Howard just pointed
with his gun
And said that way down
on Highway 61
Well Mack the Finger said
to Louie the King
I got forty red, white and
blue shoestrings
And a thousand telephones
that don't ring
Do you know where I can
get rid of these things
And Louie the King said
let me think for a minute son
And he said yes I think
it can be easily done
Just take everything
down to Highway 61
Now the fifth daughter
on the twelfth night
Told the first father that
things werent right
My complexion she said
is much too white
He said come here and
step into the light,
he says hmm youre right
Let me tell the second mother
this has been done
But the second mother was with
the seventh son
And they were both
out on Highway 61
Now the rovin gambler
he was very bored
He was tryin to create
a next world war
He found a promoter who
nearly fell off the floor
He said I never engaged
in this kind of thing before
But yes I think it can be
very easily done
Well just put some bleachers
out in the sun
And have it on Highway 61